{
    "id": "47c00620ed924236bb064ab7772d7338",
    "title": "Quantifiers Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": ".................................... people supported the project.",
            "description": "We use some before a noun without a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "Some",
                "Some of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................  my friends are vegetarians.",
            "description": "We use some of before a noun with a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "Some",
                "Some of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................... them came forward to help me.",
            "description": "We use none of before a personal pronoun.",
            "answers": [
                "None",
                "None of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I spoke to ................................ the eye witnesses.",
            "description": "We use some of before a noun with a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "some",
                "some of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Take ................................... the shirts.",
            "description": "We use any of before a noun with a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "any",
                "any of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "................................ the books in the library are missing.",
            "description": "We use some of before a noun with a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "Some",
                "Some of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "................................... the keys open the door.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "None",
                "None of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I spent ..................................... days with them last month.",
            "description": "Write a few to refer to a small number.",
            "answers": [
                "a few",
                "the few"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I drank ..................................... the milk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "some",
                "some of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................... us enjoyed the party, but I was bored.",
            "description": "We use some of before a personal pronoun.",
            "answers": [
                "Some",
                "Some of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I have invited ...................................... my friends.",
            "description": "All and all of can both be used before a noun with a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "all of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "...................................... you have passed the test.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Both",
                "Both of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}